I'm waiting by the platform.
I'm almost done changing! Sorry!!
be there soon
FRIENDS: 1
Ririsa Amano
I have a friend...
Are you Nonoa?
Nagomi-san?!
But why?!
I'll Keep Evolving
Yeah, you look exactly like Coulia.
Oh no!
Did things work out between her and Liliel?
WORRY WORRY
I guess I could ask later, but...
Did you seriously pick a fight with Liliel?
You're not even denying it.
No!
Don't give me that look.
If you're not gonna say no,
I'll take that as a yes!
Come on!
That's fine.
I get where you're coming from.
I get being jealous of other girls who
are more popular or more attractive.
I'm not, though.
But, it's gross to punch down, you know?
If you wanna pick a fight with someone,
then aim for the top and go after me!
I don't care what people think of me.
If they want me to be the bad guy,
I'll be the bad guy.
That means everyone can
team up against me and be friends.
Everyone wants attention.
You might think other cosplayers
are fighting you for that attention,
but you've got something
in common with them:
you had the courage to go out and cosplay.
That's enough to make you an ally.
A friend.
Don't forget that, okay?
Whoa...
We're friends...
Thank you.
But, you've...
You've got it all wrong.
You can speak?
Wait, what did I get wrong?
Nagomi-san, you're so freaking cool!
Where the hell did you come from?!
Oh. So you worked things out.
Wait, did you hear all that?!
What are you, stalking me?!
You did so good, Nagomi.
I'm gonna remember this when
I'm lying in bed and
fall asleep cringing about it!
Other people do that, too...
Other people do that, too.
...other people do that, too.
Nagomi-san.
Ririsa told me you gave her advice, too.
That was really nice of you.
Y-yeah, if you ever need help, just text me...
I did it.
I said the thing I needed to say.
I can speak again!
Wait, you like Liliel too, Nonoa-chan?!
Y-yeah!
I'm so thrilled!
Y-yeah, I've liked her since I was a kid...
I'm speaking, but I'm so nervous.
I haven't had a conversation in so long.
And I've never had a friend before.
B-but I'll be okay.
I know how to talk about this.
I can talk forever about Liliel.
Don't do it.
You go away!
The second you start talking,
she'll stop liking you.
Where should I start? What should I say?
There's just so many things I like,
I don't know where to start!
Between the manga, the anime, and the movie,
there's so much I could talk about.
But my favorite thing is how
she's so devoted to Lord Ashford!
You see female characters
like her in shonen manga, but...
Stop avoiding it and remember what happened!
Like, you just keep rambling,
and don't even try to connect it with our conversation.
It's like you don't even listen to us.
Conversation's supposed to go back and forth!
I know, right?
I bet instead of listening,
you're just planning out what you wanna say next.
That's not communication, you know.
R-Ririsa-chan, what do you like about Liliel?!
Oh man, so many things, I can't name just one!
I was gonna say the same thing!
You totally get it!
I'll go in story order,
HEH HEH HEH
starting with the prequel episode
bundled with the movie DVD pre-order.
Yes! I love that episode!
And you know that one awesome scene?!
Totally!
Right?!
Yeah!
I get it now.
You're not the villain.
You remembered how badly I got hurt,
and have been trying to protect me.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
I wasn't in the wrong. She was.
That's what I believed,
but it wasn't the full truth.
She was wrong to say that to me,
but what I did was wrong, too.
And when I didn't want to admit that,
I used it as an excuse to escape it all.
But it's okay.
If I make a mistake,
all I have to do is change.
I'll keep evolving.
So that's why Liliel's lines in that scene in the
new movie are both a callback to the old movie
RRRMMMBLE
AND an answer to the mixed reception the scene
in the old movie got when it was released!
Now when you go back and rewatch the
old movie it makes so much more sense!
Ten years out,
and Liliel just keeps getting deeper!
It's incredible, really!
Oh, sorry, I keep going on and on...
I wasn't that bad, was I?!
No, you're fine.
Then why are you laughing at me?!
Come on!
I won't have that nightmare again...
...because today,
I get to have fun with my friend.
Hey, Lost and Found, right?!
Did someone turn in a wallet?!
Yes, we have some wallets.
We've got lots of items today.
What did yours look like?
I also lost my phone, my train card holder,
my makeup pouch, and my keys!
These are all yours, I think?
They got turned in separately, too...
Oh, thank god!
I always make sure I
don't lose my hairpin,
but then everything else goes missing!
How?
You girls are the best.
Thanks!
She was super pretty.
She looked like she walked right out of a manga.
She's a cosplayer, right?
I didn't see her walking around, though...
Yeah, I didn't.
How the heck did we miss her?
I'm so glad I got pics of Nonoa-chan today!
And we got pics of her with Liliel!
Check out this one, the angle is perfect.
They're so cute!
Ohmigod, who are they?
They're adorbs!
Wait, that huge crowd of randos was for two girls?!
Randos?
Liliel and Nonoa, right? Cool, got it.
A gyaru just touched me...
Oh, god, an extrovert.
W-what's your handle?
Handle?
Um, you're a cosplayer, right?
Oh, yeah! I literally just started.
I'm Aria Kisaki.
Remember that name, 'cause soon,
I'm gonna be famous!
Nonoa-chan!
R-Ririsa-chan!
What cosplay is that?
I-it's just my school uniform.
It's so cute!
Thanks for coming out after school.
Sure, it wasn't that far away...
I'm so happy I could die.
Thank you for joining us for
the shoot today, Nonoa-san.
Oh, no, thank you...
Actually... Could you drop the formality a little?
I'm in the same grade as Ririsa-chan...
That's right, Senpai!
Yes, I-I mean, yeah!
I can't believe I finally get to take pictures
with another cosplayer at a real studio!
I'm so happy I have cosplay friends!
M-me too.
This is the first time I've gone
out with friends after school...
Isn't renting studio space expensive?
How much is it gonna be?
Oh, actually...
This one is run by
Mayura-sama's friend, Chika-chan.
Hey, there.
Are you the girls Mayura-chan mentioned?
Gosh, you're young.
Do I need to call the cops on her?
Nope, she hasn't done anything weird yet!
What do you mean, yet?
Oh, I know that uniform...
You know Ta-chan, the English teacher?
He and I are drinking buddies.
C-cool.
So you must be her pretty friend, Morichika-san!
Oh, sweetheart, call me Chika-chan.
I get it now.
Mayura had me crossdress anytime she
needed a guy character in her group.
Keep your mouth shut.
You'll ruin the cosplay.
Wow, rude.
Crossdress...?
Friends of hers get special discounts.
How much would it be for three
hours in the Fantasy Room?
Free fifty, honey.
Huh?!
Whatever's not booked is yours to have fun in.
Are you sure?
We own the whole building.
The tenants on the first and second floors pay rent.
I run the studio space here for fun.
I don't have time to cosplay anymore,
so the least I can do is help
out the up-and-coming newbies.
You can pay me back by getting famous, mmkay?
Thank you so much!
You can recommend me to your friends, too!
I've got a camera and can take pics
if they want to come on their own!
Oh, wow!
You did Mayura-sama's ROMs?!
Whoa... You don't need me, then.
Want my help today?
No, that's okay!
Senpai's the only person
I trust for pictures of my Liliel!
Aww, you two are cute.
If he gets hit by a truck and dies,
call me, mmkay?
Sure! I'll give you a call!
Should I worry?
Dies?
I'm gonna take pictures for a
solo cosplayer today, actually.
She's a newbie looking for friends,
but she's a little weird.
Weird?
Let me know if you wanna meet her,
and I'll arrange something.
So it's a Western fantasy theme!
They've got all this antique furniture and props, too.
I can get some great shots by the window.
Ever since Ogino-san's lesson,
I've been looking forward to
my next shoot in a studio.
Senpai's the only person
I trust for pictures of my Liliel!
If that's right, then I've really gotta
knock it out of the park today.
Wait, but Cinderella Stars Liliel is modern day,
not Western fantasy.
Or did Nonoa bring a new costume today?
Nonoa-chan, I hope you didn't
have trouble with the costume.
Sorry to ask you to make one for my series.
No, no, it's okay!
I couldn't make the weapon, though...
Because I put everything
I had into making this new outfit!
I was ready to make anything,
so long as I got to be in
a group with Liliel-chan!
Also, are you okay with getting
your photos taken by a guy?
Yeah, why?
Mikari-chan said she
wanted him to take her picture,
HMMMM
so I figured it was okay,
and I also don't want anyone
but him taking my picture...
but I need to make sure
I respect how she feels!
I didn't even think of that.
I figured that was normal for cosplay.
That's normal at events, anyways.
I totally didn't expect that!
COMPLETELY UNBOTHERED
I guess it'd be weird if I were alone with a guy...
Oh, and it doesn't really matter,
'cause Senpai's not interested in girls at all!
Okay. No idea what that means.
Still...
I feel like I can trust Okumura-senpai.
That's good.
Okay, let's get changed as fast as the wind!
We're gonna knock Senpai's socks off!
Can we get changed normally?!
Okay, we're ready, Senpai!
Sorry about the wait.
Angelic Airborne Defense Squadron Captain Nokiel!
Of course!
They're doing the Airborne Defense Squadron
from the spinoff!
There are so many more
female characters in that series!
It's perfect for a group cosplay!
No, more than perfect!
How could I have missed this?!
Is he okay?
It's so simple! I'm a fool!
We'll get started once he's done freaking out.
An utter fool!
Okay, let's get started.
Okay, Senpai!
I think the spot by the window could be good!
It was hard to tell in the manga and anime,
but Nokiel's a bit taller than Liliel.
It's cool seeing it in real life!
And the studio set makes it look like
a scene straight from the anime!
Next up...
Nonoa-chan, can I hug you?
Y-yeah, sure!
Nokiel!
Nokiel, thank you!
Liliel-sama, your ch-chest...
This is straight out of the manga!
Liliel hugged me...
Senpai, can I see the picture?
Already? Sure.
We look so good!
You're incredible, Senpai!
Text this one to me!
I'm a little embarrassed to look at pictures of myself...
But this is so much fun.
I'm so happy.
Um, could you send that picture to me?
Yeah, sure.
Nokiel's talking to me!
Cosplay is crazy.
I can't believe this is the same person.
Can I post this picture online?
Sure, go ahead!
You've got a social media account?
Can I see it?
Sure, but it's pretty boring.
my stomach hurts
just had dinner
Your feed reminds me
hungry
of a house made of plain concrete.
overslept
I got a lot of followers after
I was featured on that blog,
so I've been too nervous to post anything...
Are you dead?
Tons of people are asking if you're dead.
Do you have an account, Ririsa-chan?
Yeah, I've got one!
It's basically a Liliel reaction account though.
liliel addict
Event coming up, so probably not gonna post...
Liliel liliel liliel liliel
I'm not gonna make an account for my cosplay.
Liliel doesn't have social media, after all.
Are you trying to become an urban legend?
I think it's great that Nagomi-san gets
to wear all these different outfits...
But I don't want people to
think of me when I cosplay.
I want to be the character.
Instead of thinking "Ririsa's here!",
I want people to think "the real-life Liliel is here!"
She's cosplaying Liliel for the series and fans...
I picked Coulia because I wouldn't have to talk,
and Nokiel because it looked doable...
I didn't put enough thought into this.
I feel horrible.
Why did she even want to be friends with me?
There's no way she'll like me.
I'm sorry. That's not right.
I'm going to be someone new.
I just need to be someone who's
worthy of being Liliel's partner.
Nokiel is a knight who's sworn
to protect Lilel with her life.
She's my first and only friend.
I'll protect her, no matter what.
I will protect you with my life, Liliel-sama.
How'd I miss that perfect moment?!
No way, Liliel and Nonoa?! For realsies?!
Hold it, Aria-chan, I need to ask if it's okay first!
Who's that?
A voice that loud has to mean trouble...
Sorry, I tried to stop her.
Is it okay if we interrupt?
They're really here!
Can I be your friend?!
I'm Aria!
I've been looking for you guys!
She's gorgeous!
Look at her big eyes...
And her perfect body!
A gyaru?! No wonder I'm shivering...
What's a gyaru doing here?!
Y-you were looking for us?
Yeah, duh!
I just started cosplaying,
and went to that Cinderella Stars event, right?
That's where I saw a pic of you guys and ohmigod,
it was totally love at first sight!
I just had to be friends with you!
Friends?!
I found Nonoa's account,
but her DMs were closed so I couldn't message her.
I closed them so I don't get
messages from people like you!
It's crazy we're here at the same time.
It's like, destiny, right?
We're basically already friends!
What up, bestie?!
O-okay...
I nearly died getting there with her,
and she got there within five seconds!
How is she already hanging off her?!
Extroverts are truly terrifying...
Wait, wait, ohmigosh,
let's take photos together!
R-right now?! We're kinda...
Look.
I don't think you know,
but we're actually
cosplaying from the same series.
Your cosplay isn't from the Liliel spinoff, right?
Then you can't take pictures with us.
Wait, really?!
C'mon, who cares if we're from the same series?
It'll be just like the Avengers!
Those are all Marvel characters!
I give up.
I'm an introverted otaku who didn't watch the Avengers
and I don't want to hang out with someone
who compares things to the Avengers.
Nonoa-chan, come back to us!
Why...?
Why did a random hyper gyaru
have to show up right now?
The whole reason I'm an otaku cosplayer is
because I don't get along with girls like her.
Nonoa-chan?
Girls like her like to get in your personal space
and use slang you've never even heard of,
and at school they act as if they're the
best and otaku are lesser human beings...
We can never be friends.
Hold on a second, Nonoa-chan!
Who did this to you?!
Who's the villain?!
Give me their name!
This girl in my class, Tanaka-san.
But she isn't Tanaka-san!
You don't know if she's going to be like that!
Yeah...
You're right, Liliel-chan.
I shouldn't be so quick to judge.
Right?
Give her a chance,
maybe you'll be friends!
Aria-chan, why did you get into cosplay?
Is it because you like anime and manga?
I-I guess manga?
I read a lot of it when I was little.
But I wanna be a famous cosplayer!
Famous?
You guys just started and you're
already getting up there, right?
That's why I wanted to find you and hit you up!
See? We're completely different species.
But she's being upfront with us,
and she doesn't seem like a bad person!
I know, but...
I was really excited to get to do
a shoot with the two of us...
Nonoa-chan...
Oh, geez, the girls are fighting...
Ririsa.
I know you want to be nice to everyone,
but you made plans with Nonoa today.
You should tell her sorry, but no,
and make plans for another time.
Senpai...
Yeah, you're right.
Aww, what a guy. You go, girl.
Besides, when you're going after a girl in a game,
you can only do one route at a time!
You're right!
He could've done without the example...
But if it works for her, then sure.
Sorry, Nonoa-chan...
Aria-san!
Hey, just call me Aria!
If Liliel-chan can't do it, then I'll protect her!
Whoa, you look so good!
How'd you do your makeup?
Listen to me!
I don't know what you're thinking, Aria-san.
You're drop-dead gorgeous.
I bet you could go outside and
instantly get scouted for modeling.
Nono-pi, you think I'm gorgeous?!
Listen!
Why cosplay, then?!
You're already attractive as you are!
If you want to be famous, just be an idol,
or a model, or an actress!
I can't.
It has to be cosplay.
I don't want to be on TV or in magazines, just...
Never mind.
Well, if you care that much about it,
I guess we could take pictures together.
No way, for real?!
I guess if Nonoa's okay with it...
So, uh, I'll get changed, but...
But what?
T-there's a guy in here.
There's a changing room!
Oh, right, I forgot!
She's shyer about it than Ririsa!
Women's Changing Room
Your Way, My Way